http://store.waterpumpsupply.com/privacypolicy.html

Home > This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering
system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but
may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store
through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information
about your shopping experience. Please see the
Yahoo! Privacy Policy for more
information about how Yahoo! uses this information.
Privacy Policy
1.
Commitment to Privacy:
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
2.
Information Collected:
The types of personal information we collect include all the information entered on the Order Form pages: shipping and billing name and address, email address, phone number and credit card information. We collect this information from you using the Yahoo! Store hosting and backend services.
3.
Uses of Information:
We use the information you provide when placing an order to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order or to provide services where the outside party is acting on our behalf and has no independent right to use the information we provide (i.e. a third party shipping or customer support center).
We use aggregate information to better design our website and to share with potential business partners. For example, we may tell a potential partner that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of people from a certain zip code purchased certain items, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
We may contact you from time to time regarding your order status or about products or specials that we think you may be interested in. If you do not wish to receive these notifications, we will honor your request not to send them to you.
We use return email addresses from your email correspondence to us to answer the email we receive. Such addresses from your correspondence are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
Finally, we do not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without providing you an opportunity to tell us not to allow such unrelated uses.
4. Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information from our online store from those we actually know are under the age of 13.
5.
Data Security:
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
6.
Relationship to Yahoo!:
This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store
pages, ordering system, and order data.Yahoo!automatically
collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please
see the http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.
7.
Access and Data Correction:
You can access and correct your order and contact information by contacting us. You can also access your order history on Yahoo!
Shopping if you are a registered Yahoo! user.
8.
Contact Information:
Should you have other questions or concerns about this our privacy policies, please return to our store (using your browser's "BACK" button) and contact us directly using the contact information posted there.
9.
Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, click here.
Pumps by ManufacturerAMT PumpsAmerican Granby AST Technology
Berkeley PumpsBlue Angel PumpsBrady ProductsBurks PumpsCalpeda PumpsCTS FabricationCla-Val RegulatorsConery ManufacturingCrane PumpsFlexible Pump ConnectorsFlint & Walling PumpsFlo Control ValvesFlojet PumpsFranklin Electric MotorsGorman-Rupp PumpsGoulds Water TechnologyGreen Leaf FittingsGrundfos Pumps Hayward Pumps Heller Aller PumpsHonda Engine PumpsHudson ValvesIntermatic TimersJabsco Pumps Kalas Wire & CableLeader PumpsLiberty PumpsLittle Giant PumpsMP PumpsMTH PumpsMercoid SwitchesMyers PumpsOasis PumpsOberdorfer PumpsOTS PumpsPacer PumpsPedrollo PumpsPearl PumpsPentair PumpsPower-Flo PumpsProtek PumpsRule Pumps SJ Electro SwitchesSimer Pumps StaRite PumpsStrataflo ProductsTopp Plastic BasinsWatts RegulatorsWellMate Pressure TanksWessel Pressure TanksWilo PumpsXylem PumpsZoeller PumpsPumps By BrandAce-In-A-HoleAMTAquaBoostAquaCharge American Granby Ante-SeizeBerkeleyBlue AngelBradyBurksCharge N' FlowChemFloCTSCLA-VALConeryCraneDrainosaur PumpsEcoSub Sump PumpsFlint and WallingFlo ControlFlojetFlomax Franklin ElectricGorman RuppGoulds Water TechnologyGreen LeafGrundfosHeller AllerHondaHudson ValvesHydrotronic ControlIntermaticIrrigator PumpsJabscoKalasLeaderLibertyLittle GiantMP MTHMercoidMyersOasisOberdorferOilTectorOmnivore OTSPearlPacerPedrolloPentairPonyPower-FloProtekRainPerfectRanger Rule Rule-A-Matic SwitchRustler SJE RhombusSimerStaRite StratafloSuper BruteSuperMaxToppWater WizardWattsWellmateWesselWiloXylemZoellerPumps By Type12 Volt DC PumpsBattery Operated Bottle Water Pumps Centrifugal PumpsCondensate PumpsComputerized PumpsDeep Well PumpsDemand PumpsDiaphragm PumpsDrum PumpsDual Purpose PumpsEffluent PumpsEngine Driven PumpsFountain PumpsGear PumpsGrinder PumpsHand PumpsInline Circulating PumpsJet PumpsMacerator PumpsMagnetic Drive PumpsMultistage PumpsPeripheral Turbine PumpsPiston PumpsPool Cover PumpsPool and Spa PumpsPositive DisplacementPitcher PumpsPond PumpsRotary PumpsRubber Impeller PumpsSeal-less PumpsSelf Priming PumpsSmall Submersible PumpsSolid Handling PumpsStatuary PumpsSeptic Tank PumpsSubmersible PumpsSewage PumpsSubmersible Well Pumps
Sump Pumps Trash PumpsVariable Speed PumpsWaterfall PumpsWater PumpsPumps By UseAgricultural Aquarium Barrel BilgesBoiler Feed BoostersBottle Water ChemicalCondensateContractorDemandDewatering Diesel FuelDrumEffluentElevator SumpFountainsHot Water CirculationIrrigationJockey PumpsMarineOil TransferPondsPool and SpaRain BarrelSeptic Tank SewageShower DrainSolar Powered Sprinkler StatuaryStorm WaterSumpPressure TestingTransferUnder The Sink Waterfall Well PumpsPumps By MaterialAluminum PumpsAluminum Cast Iron FittedBrassBronze PumpsCast Iron Water PumpsCast Iron Bronze FittedPlastic PumpsPlastic Fitted PumpsStainless Steel
304 PumpsStainless Steel 316 PumpsStainless 304 Plastic FittedNickle Plated Pumps by MarketIrrigation Market
PumpsMarine Residential PumpsBuilding Trade Commercial Construction Industrial Sewage Water Gardening AccessoriesAir Volume ControlsAquastat ControlsCheck & Foot ValvesDuplex Control Panels Electrical Controls Electrical Splicing TapeFlexible TubingFranklin Boxes Franklin Motors Heat Shrink KitsHose AdaptersSuction & Discharge HosesHudson Float ValvesJet Pumps AccessoriesLeader Accessories Liquid Level AlarmsLevel SwitchesMonodrive Controller PVC Ball Valves PVC FittingsPitless Well AdaptersPolypropylene FittingsPressure GaugesPressure ReducersPressure Switches Pressure TanksPriming Tee Pump CoverPump Motor CoversPumpTec ControlsSprinkler Pump Accessories Sprinkler Pump TimerSubmersible Cable Sump/Sewage AccessoriesValvesWell CapsWell Pump AccessoriesWell Seals
Customer ReviewsRead more...
Home|About Us|Contact Us|Terms of Use|Terms of Sale|Privacy Policy|Shipping Policy|FAQ
Internet prices apply only to Internet purchases.
Minimum order amount is $20.00.
All merchandise listed is in stock.
Orders are shipped the next business day.
We only sell within the 48 adjacent United States.
Shipping tracking numbers are e-mailed automatically.
Office hours are: Mon - Fri, 8am - 5pm EST excl. holidays.
Copyright © 2012 All Rights Reserved.
Yahoo Store Development & Design: TIMES
